We often try to save money for a variety of different reasons.
我们总会出于各种各样的原因存钱。
It might be to save up for a new computer, put money aside into a rainy-day fund or put a deposit down for a mortgage on a house.
可能是为了攒钱买一台新电脑，为应急基金预留一笔钱，或是为买房的按揭贷款支付首付。
Learning how to save is important, but a recent study showed that over half of all 22 – 29-year-olds living in the UK have no savings at all.
学会存钱至关重要，但最近一项研究显示，在英国22至29岁的人群中，超过半数的人根本没有存款。
Did they splurge and splash out on too many things, or are there other factors?
是他们挥霍无度、花钱大手大脚，还是另有原因？
And how can we become better savers?
我们又该如何成为更会存钱的人呢？
Many young people in the UK choose to live away from home, and the cost of renting can impact the amount we can tuck away in our savings.
许多英国年轻人选择离家独居，高昂的房租会直接影响我们能存下的钱数。
On top of that, according to a 2017 study, there is a huge pay gap in people in their twenties in the UK, with the top 10% earning 4.3 times per week as the lowest earners.
此外，2017年的一项研究表明，英国二十多岁年轻人的收入差距悬殊，收入最高的10%人群周薪是收入最低人群的4.3倍。
Possibly the mentality of ‘saving more when I earn more’ has crept in.
或许正是“等赚得多了再多存钱”的心态在悄然作祟。
However, there were some positives, with the number of people in debt, not including student loans for university, having fallen from 49% 10 years ago to 37%.
不过也有一些积极的趋势：不含大学助学贷款在内的负债人群比例，已从十年前的49%降至如今的37%。
So, how can we improve our ability to save?
那么，我们该如何提升存钱能力呢？
First off, put a stop to those impulse buys.
首先，杜绝冲动消费。
Ask yourself if you really need to buy something, even if it is on sale or looks like a bargain.
就算商品正在打折，或是看起来很划算，也要先问问自己是否真的需要。
One way you could control your spending urges is by using cash rather than card.
控制消费欲望的一个办法是使用现金而非银行卡支付。
Withdrawing cash before you go to a restaurant or shopping sets a fixed budget you must adhere to.
去餐厅吃饭或购物前先取好现金，这样就能设定一个必须遵守的固定预算。
Also, any change that comes from your transactions when you’re using cash can be put in jar and deposited into your account.
此外，用现金交易时收到的零钱可以放进存钱罐，之后再存入银行账户。
Finally, setting up a standing order from your current account into your savings just after you receive your salary will ensure you have some money set aside for a time that you might need it.
最后，在发薪后立即设置自动转账，把钱从活期账户转入储蓄账户，这样就能确保为不时之需存下一笔钱。
Just after getting paid is a good idea for this as it means you save before you’ve had the chance to spend.
发薪之后马上就转是一个好主意，因为这意味着你还没有花钱的机会，钱就已经被存起来了。
While there is some good news about debt for the twenty-somethings in the UK, the fact that over half have no savings is seen as a cause for concern.
尽管英国二十多岁人群的负债情况有了些许好转，但半数以上的人毫无存款这一事实，依然引发了人们的担忧。
While it could be due to some economic disparity, there may be some other factors at play.
这或许是经济差距造成的，但也可能涉及其他因素。
However, there are some actions we can take to help us all become better savers.
不过，我们确实可以采取一些措施，让自己变得更擅长储蓄。